Hello.
こんにちは
I'm surrounded by amazing equipment though.
すごい機材に囲まれていますけどね
What do you think?
どうです?
How do you feel like this?
こんな、どんな気分ですか?
I want to be nervous.
緊張したいです
ah.
ああ
He's a really pushy person.
本当に押しとやかな人ですよね
Really quiet.
本当に静かな
Well, this kind of thing doesn't usually happen.
まあ、こういうのは普通しないもんね
In a situation like this.
こういうシチュエーションでね
Ordinary people too.
一般人も
ah.
ああ
Are you closed today too?
今日もお休みですか?
Everyone at this part-time job says it's dazzling.
このバイトってみんな眩しいって言うんですよ
Camera guys.
カメラみんな
It's dazzling.
眩しいです
Is it dazzling?
眩しいですか?
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
What should I do?
どうしたらいいの?
effect.
こうか
How much is it?
どれくらいなんですか?
Well, in moderation.
まあ、ほどほどにします
Is it close?
近いですか?
No.
違います
It's cute.
可愛いもん
dazzling.
眩しい
It's really beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗ですね
Can I just have a moment?
ちょっとだけいいですか?
It's black.
黒いですね
There are 100 people.
100人です
There are three of us.
3人ですね
So, you're the fourth person.
じゃあ、4人目ってことですね
Have you ever done anything without wearing rubber?
ゴムつけずにやったことっていうのは今までないんですか?
that's right.
そうです
I'll take it off for a while.
ちょっと外しちゃいます
face.
顔
again.
改めて
nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
It's not hot.
熱くないですね
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
What's this?
何がちょっとこう
It's okay to ask questions.
質問とか大丈夫ですね
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Well, from now on, uncle,
じゃあ今から、ちょっとおじさん、
I'm going to teach you about the fear of being an adult.
大人の怖さを教えていくんで
dazzling.
眩しい
It must be dazzling.
眩しいでしょうね
If I don't include this, I can't really see it.
これが入れないとね、なかなか見えなくて
difficult.
難しい
It's like that.
そんな感じです
It's stylish.
おしゃれです
successfully.
うまく
nice.
いいね
It's expensive.
高いですね
This is an expensive-looking fabric.
高そうな生地ですね、これ
It's kind of like that.
なんか、あれですね
It's full of youthfulness.
若さが溢れててますね
It's full of youth.
若さが溢れててます
Let's take it again.
もう一度取っちゃおこう
I like taking this.
これ取っていくの好きなんですよ
My abdominal muscles are torn.
腹筋割れてますね
It's not broken.
割れてないです
But it's kind of amazing.
でもなんか、すごいね
Down below.
下に
wonderful.
素晴らしい
I just need to be patient.
ちょっと耐えればいいな
Good.
よいしょ
Well then, I'll keep those clothes for you.
じゃあ、その服を預かります
I'll leave it there first.
先に置いておきますね
Everyone has a beautiful body.
みんな、綺麗な体だもんね
There's no point in leaving anything behind.
残しとかなきゃ駄目ですもん
Everyone, after all, I'm going to be obase.
みんな、やっぱりね、おばせになるんで
That's good.
いい ですね
I have verified my follow.
フォロー認証してしまってました
Hime-chan, just a little.
ひめちゃん、ちょっとね
That's fine.
そこでいいんで
Is it okay if I stand up?
お立ちになっていただいても大丈夫ですか?
This gives this DK a luxurious look.
これは、このDKに姿を豪華させますね、
this.
これ
If you are at sea like this,
海にこんな形でいらっしゃったら、
I'm so excited.
ドキドキしますね
Can I have a look at the person behind you?
後ろの方も見てもらっていいですか?
Can I have a look at this too?
こ っちも見てもらっていいですか?
May I ask you to sit down?
お座りになってもらっていいですか?
Have you ever seen anything like this?
こんなワガワガと見たことありますか?
Which should I choose?
どっちにしよう?
Have you ever seen one up close like this?
こんな近くで見たことはありますか?
I thought I'd have it verified.
検証していってもらうかなと思って
Who is that woman?
誰ですよ、そんな女性
Do you understand even if you are surprised?
びっくりとなっても分かるんですか?
I don't know, so not much.
分かんないから、あまり
Well then, have your hand behind me,
じゃあ、後ろに手ついてもらって、
Can I help you for a moment?
ちょっと足をしてもらっていいですか?
Can I have it opened for you?
開いてもらっていいですか?
A woman who is evasive.
逃げあごな、そんな女性
That's hectic.
ヘッチだなぁ
Well then, I guess I'll take this as well.
じゃあ、これも取っちゃおうかな
Is it a hand?
手かな?
This panty.
このパンテー
Is it okay if I take it?
取っちゃってもいいかな
Just be careful.
ちょっと気を付けて
Can I have a little grin?
ちょっとニヤカダしもらっていいですか?
Let's take it home.
持って帰ろう
Please be a little careful.
ちょっと気を付けてですね
Please suffer.
苦しんでください
It would be embarrassing if this was thrown at me,
この投げられたら恥ずかしいよね、
surely.
確かに
I don't usually have it
普段ないもん
hey.
ね
But, can I tell you one thing?
でも、 1つ言っていいかな
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だよね
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
Doesn't your neck hurt from that posture?
首痛くないですか、その姿勢
Can you see it?
見えますか?
I want you to come closer to me.
近寄ってきて欲しいです
What did you think?
なんて思ったの?
You remember, right?
覚えてるでしょ?
Wow, everyone has surpassed it.
うわぁ、みんな超えてる
Give me a little lick.
ちょっとペロペロして
Lick it.
ペロペロして
face.
顔を
顔 を
That's amazing.
すごいね
Just a little while.
ちょっとじゃあね
It's in between.
この間に入ってる
Ah, that's right.
あ、そっ
This isn't a car, so you can let all your saliva flow.
ここは車じゃないから、 唾液は全部で垂れ流していいから
I'll cut it slowly.
ゆっくり切るからね
Wow, that's amazing.
うわぁ、すごいね
Aren't you good at it?
上手じゃないか
My head might slip.
頭が滑れるかもしれない
line in the middle.
真ん中の線
This popularity.
この人気
Well then, shall I say it now?
じゃあさ、もう言いちゃおうか
Do you want to climb on top of me and ride it in the future?
今後もさ、上に乗って、乗ってみる?
Have you ever ridden?
乗ったことある?
Have you ever run a business?
企業したことある?
small.
小さい
narrow.
狭い
Yes.
はい ね
Are you getting tired?
疲れてきた?
It's here.
ここですね
show me.
見せて
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗だね
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
Can I go now?
そろそろ行ってもいい?
good?
いい?
Even if I go.
行 っても
No, I'm leaving.
ダメだ、行っちゃうよ
there were.
あ った
For the first time in my life.
人生初にも
are you tired?
疲れましたか?
I'm really tired.
めっちゃ疲れてますね
It's about time.
そ ろそろ
You must be quite tired.
結構疲れてるでしょ
Please take a break.
ちょっと休んでくださいね
Shall we say goodbye?
さよならしましょうか
I'll sleep with you again.
またおねえしますね
See you then.
じゃあね